FACUNDO ARAGON

Full Stack Web Developer

Email: <u>facundo_aragon@hotmail.com</u> GitHub: <u>facuaragon</u>

Portfolio: <u>facundoaragon.com.ar</u> Ubicación: Buenos Aires, Argentina LinkedIn: <u>Facundo Aragon</u> Phone: +54 9 11 6641 4910

Full Stack Developer with a background in Web Design. Experienced in working with technologies such as React, Redux, NodeJs, Express, PostgreSQL, Next.js, MongoDB, among others in the field. Currently, I am in a continuous learning process, working on personal projects to solidify what I've learned and expand my knowledge. I'm a sociable and proactive individual who works well in a team, embraces challenges, and excels at problem-solving. I acquired these skills during my previous work experience in the construction sector, where I performed physical tasks on-site. As a Site Manager, I successfully completed projects on time and within the budget, leading teams of architects, administrative staff, and subcontractors to execute all tasks.

PROJECTS

Oct-2023 E-Commerce – Jr. Full Stack Web Developer – Personal Project

Design and development of an e-commerce store where users can view products, add them to the cart, and make payments using Mercado Pago. The project includes an admin panel for adding and editing products.

Repository: Client / Admin Deploy: E-Commerce

Sept-2023 Portfolio for Journalist – Jr. Full Stack Web Developer – Freelance Project

Design and development of a website for a journalist. Developed using Next.js, React,

MongoDB, HTML, CSS.

Repository: Fran Ferreyra Deploy: soyfranferreyra

Ago-2023 Portfolio Personal – Jr. Full Stack Web Developer – *Personal Project*

Design and development of my personal portfolio to showcase my information, projects, skills, and contact information. Developed using Next.js, React, Nodemailer, HTML, CSS.

Repository: Facundo Aragon Deploy: Portfolio

Jul-2023 Devter - Jr. Full Stack Web Developer - Personal Project

Design and development of a Twitter clone for developers. Utilized technologies like Next.js,

React, Firebase Auth, Firestore Database, Realtime Database, HTML, CSS.

Repository: <u>Devter</u> <u>Devter</u>

Jun-2023 Consumedic - Trainee Full Stack Web Developer - Henry Bootcamp - Group Final Project

Design and development of a web application that allows users to book appointments with healthcare professionals, including third-party authentication, Mercado Pago, Cloudinary, admin panel, profiles for doctors and patients, email functionality, local storage, and logical deletion. I specifically worked on database modeling, relationships, and defining server request routes with their respective logic. I developed the calendar component for each doctor in both the backend and frontend. I was also responsible for developing the Doctor Panel where patient information, medical history, appointments, and the ability to send messages and upload files were displayed.

Repository: PF-soyHenry Deploy: Consumedic

May-2023 Dogs - Trainee Full Stack Web Developer - Henry Bootcamp - Proyecto Individual

Design and development of a web application for dog breeds, including combined searches, filtering, sorting, and a form for creating new breeds. Technologies used include React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS..

Repository: <u>Backend</u> / <u>Frontend</u> Deploy: <u>WikiDOG</u>

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 Novadomus S.R.L.

Site Manager

Directorio 223, Caballito, CABA, Argentina. 13-story building with 2 basements.

Constructed Area: 7.006m2

- Led the final construction phase of the project.
- Planned and organized the team for the site and its resources, ensuring the completion of Functional Units and their delivery to owners

2019-2021 OBRAS Y SISTEMAS S.R.L.

Jefe de Obra

Aranguren 1337, Caballito, CABA, Argentina. 2-story building with 2 basements. 2-story building with 2 basements: 4.315,21m²

• Managed the project from the beginning. Led a team of professionals and site personnel. Despite delays due to the COVID-19 pandemic, we completed the project within the budget with excellent.

2015-2018 OBRAS Y SISTEMAS S.R.L.

Assistant Site Manager

Av. de Mayo 1145, Monserrat, CABA, Argentina. 12-story building with 6 basements. Constructed Area: 9.093,00m²

- Led the excavation tasks, which presented numerous challenges.
- Managed the hiring and supervision of subcontractors for various project installations.
- Oversaw the delivery of 16 containers sent from Germany for the construction of the Automated Parking and planned the unloading operations and equipment storage logistics on-site.

2014-2015 OBRAS Y SISTEMAS S.R.L.

Site Supervisor

Av. Rivadavia 2355, Balvanera, CABA, Argentina. 27-story tower building with 3 basements. Constructed Area: 28,274.89m²

- Supervised various construction processes, specializing in quality control and planning the delivery of materials necessary for reinforced concrete structure execution.
- Through scheduling, logistics, and control of suppliers and contractors responsible for structure execution, we completed it within the expected deadlines.

2014 OBRAS Y SISTEMAS S.R.L.

Technical Office - Bidding Department

- Participated in the preparation of bids by calculating and budgeting for projects and updated cost analyses.
- During my short time in the Technical Office, we were awarded two major projects.

2011-2012 Agua y Saneamientos Argentinos S.A.

Young Professionals Contract - Planning Department

 Prepared bid documents. Had a very active role in the ACUBA Industrial Collector project (Wilde)

EDUCATION

2023 Soy Henry

Full Stack Web Developer

2008- 2013 UNIVERSIDAD CATÓLICA ARGENTINA

Civil Engineering Pending Final Project

2007 COLEGIO CHAMPAGNAT

High School with a Focus on Economics

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH Excellent oral and written proficiency.

Exams:

- 2023 EF Standard English Test: C2-Proficient
- 2018 International English Testing System (IELTS)
- 2004 First Certificate in English (FCE)